stopthehacker.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy

Since November 2013, StopTheHacker (STH) has been a wholly owned subsidiary of CloudFlare, Inc. This privacy policy outlines our general policy and practices for the types of information CloudFlare gathers in the course of offering its STH products and services, how we use it and the notice and choice affected individuals have regarding our use of and their ability to correct that information.

**CloudFlare privacy & security policy**

CloudFlare will not sell, rent, or give away any of your personal information without your consent. It is our overriding privacy principle that any personal information you provide to us is just that: personal and private. We do not presume that you are granting us permission to share your personal information with third parties wanting to sell you products or services that you have not requested. In order for us to provide some of the services we do we may on occasion need to provide information you supply us to external parties. While these third parties will have access to customer information in order to perform the functions CloudFlare contracts to them, such data may not be used by them for other purposes. CloudFlare may need to purge information from its system from time to time, and does not promise to keep any information beyond what is required by applicable law or regulation.  
CloudFlare’s website and services are not intended for, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 18. CloudFlare does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 18.

**PERSONS TO WHOM THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES**

This privacy policy applies to visitors to our website, users of CloudFlare’s services, and information we collect from visitors to the websites of users of CloudFlare’s services. Our users’ websites may have their own Privacy Policies and may not be covered by CloudFlare’s policy. We encourage visitors to these third party websites to make themselves aware of their privacy policies.

**INFORMATION DESIGNATED AS PUBLIC**

As part of our service, our users may decide to provide information specifically to be shared with third parties. For example, they may allow us to build statistical reports based on what malicious visitors have visited your site or how many visitors’ computers may have been infected by a particular site. In cases such at these, we will try to make it clear whenever any information our users provide us will be made public. Even when our users give us permission to make certain information public, we will still protect the information designated private (such as name, email address, IP address, and other information specifically tagged to the user’s identity) from being disclosed.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

CloudFlare is the owner of the information collected through the STH Service. As visitors browse our web site, or our user’s websites if they have STH installed, we sometimes log these visitors’ interactions in order to provide a better service (e.g., using visitor log data in order to detect new threats). Some examples of the types of information we collect for STH services include:

• Customer Provided Data. Customers using STH services that require registration may provide identifying or payment information (such as a name, email or mailing address, credit card information, account password, etc.).

• Information Tracked with Cookies. For information on what we track with cookies see the section specifically on cookies below.

• Server Log Data. STH’s servers may automatically log information from a customer’s browser during a visit to our website. The resulting server logs may include information such as a customer’s web requests, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of web requests and cookies that may uniquely identify the customer’s browser.

• Information Received from Others. CloudFlare may receive data that customers of the STH website have provided to third parties, such as vendor partners of STH. While such third parties may have their own privacy policies, we will, for our part, treat all such information as if it were provided directly from the customer to STH under this Privacy Policy.

**BILLING INFORMATION**

CloudFlare collects and maintains certain information from our users for the purposes of billing. We may report this information to third party processors for the limited purpose of receiving payment. CloudFlare does not store full credit card numbers or personal account numbers (PANs).

**CORRECTIONS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION**

This web site makes it easy to correct any mistakes in your personal information at any time. Whenever possible, we will give you an opportunity to review and change any information you provide to us. If you notice a mistake in the information you provide us, you can always revise it. This can be done either online or contacting us directly.

**COOKIES**

Our site uses “cookies” in order to provide a better service to our users. Cookies are placed by your browser on your computer’s hard drive to assign a unique identification for your computer. CloudFlare does not store information we consider personal or private in a cookie. This eliminates the chance of other sites reading our cookies and learning your personal or private information, without permission. For example, we may use cookies to help direct you to the appropriate part of our web site, by indicating that you are a repeat visitor to our site. We also may use that information to present you with services which are easy-to-use and customized to your preferences.  
STH only stores Temporary Session IDs in cookies. These Temporary Session IDs map to customer data stored on our servers. For example, we send one or more cookies to visitors to the STH site in order to uniquely identify their browsers so that we can remember customer preferences.

If you do not want CloudFlare or other websites to use cookies, you can disable them within your browser. Some portions of the STH website are still functional without cookies; however, many parts of the website will not function properly. You may delete CloudFlare’s cookies through your browser’s cookie manager. Be aware that this will reset your session, disable auto-login, and may adversely affect other functions on the CloudFlare website and services.

As part of our service, may place cookies on the browsers of your visitors to your CloudFlare-protected sites. STH provides a [Trust Seal](https://www.stopthehacker.com/features/#3664 "STH Trust Seal") for use on our customers’ websites. Displaying the Seal shows visitors that the website is protected by STH’s advanced security product and scanned regularly. When your website displays the STH Trust Seal, CloudFlare may place cookies on the browsers of your visitors to your STH-protected sites. We do this to in order to track malicious visitors, to reduce the chance of blocking legitimate users, and to provide customized services.

**DATA AGGREGATION**

CloudFlare may aggregate data we acquire about our users. When our users display the STH Trust Seal, we may aggregate data about our users and the visitors to their sites. For example, we may assemble data to determine how spiders crawl the Internet and whether they are engaged in malicious activity. If we assemble this sort of data and provide it to external parties, our user’s personal information (such as their name, email address, IP address, and other information specifically tagged to your identity) will never be attached to or included in the aggregated data. Please note, public data our users provide us, such as log files of their site’s visitors, may be included in the aggregate data, reports and statistics.

**PROMOTIONAL PARTNERS**

From time to time, CloudFlare may notify you about an offer from one of our promotional partners (e.g., Apps Marketplace partners) via our website or email. While we may target particular types of users for these offers, we will do all of the targeting within our system. Our business partners will not have any access to the targeting information, including the names of the people who may be interested in a particular product or service. Until you affirmatively respond to a promotional offer, we will not reveal any identifying information about you to any of these partners.  
Note these partners may have their own Privacy Policies and may not be covered by CloudFlare’s policy.

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

The CloudFlare website, STH website, and the other websites contain links to the sites of third parties. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these external sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of other websites. We cannot guarantee that these third parties abide by the privacy principles outlined here.

**LAW ENFORCEMENT**

It is possible that CloudFlare may be required by court order to provide information about our customers. CloudFlare may also be required to provide information pursuant to law, applicable regulation, subpoena or other legal process. It is CloudFlare’s corporate policy to ensure adherence to the due process of law in all such legal requests. If we are ever required to provide information under these circumstances, we will, whenever possible, attempt to inform users whose information we are compelled to reveal.

**DATA SECURITY, DATA INTEGRITY, AND ACCESS**

CloudFlare takes all reasonable steps to protect our users’ information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure such information. CloudFlare only processes personal information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by the individual. CloudFlare allows our users and website visitors access to their personal information and allows them to correct, amend or delete inaccurate information, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the privacy of the individual in the case in question or where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated.

**SAFE HARBOR FRAMEWORK**

CloudFlare is now a [Safe Harbor](http://export.gov/safeharbor/) certified company. We follow the U.S.-E.U. and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce. This applies to all personal information received by CloudFlare whether in electronic, paper, or verbal format. As part of our [participation](https://www.export.gov/safehrbr/list.aspx/) in the Safe Harbor, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Framework. If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor you should first contact us (as provided below). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by Internet [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request), fax to 415-520-3420, or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., click [here](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us) for mailing address. If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe’s dispute resolution process, click [here](http://www.truste.com/why_TRUSTe_privacy_services/online-privacy-watchdog.html) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

We will always maintain the overriding principle that we will not sell, rent, or give away any personal information you share with us without your consent. We do not believe we will need to change that principle going forward. However, if we do need to change any other aspect of the policy, we will post changes on this website along with the effective date of those changes.

**Keeping your information private and secure**

• We will never sell, rent, or give away your personal information without your permission  
• We track visitors to our site and yours as a feature of the STH Trust Seal in order to keep malicious visitors away  
• If we aggregate data, we will not reveal your private information

Have questions?

If you have questions about these terms or anything else about CloudFlare, please don’t hesitate to contact us:  
Contact information

Attention: Trust and Safety  
StopTheHacker, Inc.  
665 Third Street, Suite 200  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
privacy@stopthehacker.com

Policy date: September 11, 2014
